So my name is Sachin and today I have brought
you another news related to insurance.
Yes friends, the ICICI Lombard
Board has taken over the non-life business of Indian education i.e.
general insurance business
which includes car insurance and your health
insurance and your insurance i.e.
fire and marine, all the businesses,
or
they have given approval for it. Now they will
file this idea and when the idea gets
approved, then all the
products and
portfolio of the Indian Army will come under it
and the customers will also
get the services from ICICI Lombard only. By doing
this, the entire IAS Long
Hard will become the
third largest player in our general insurance industry.
In private sector,
it is still the largest player but still
some government
insurance companies
like New India Insurance and
National Insurance, they
complete their business somewhere or the other, so
what will happen with its arrival, ICICI will become the third largest player in the entire industry
and because of this
Lombard will
get a big boost in business, so I hope that
this information of mine would have added some knowledge to you
and please stay connected
with my channel, please subscribe to it
so that here you will keep getting
every news related to insurance, every product, every thing,
reviews and information, thank you
very much for watching this video.